[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What does that tell you as a prominent lawyer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, it tells me that the special prosecutor is not going to use a copout.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "If you were representing him, how would you be feeling tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Well, I think it's bad news for Zimmerman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "If that is proven to be the case, if those facts are proved by evidence, will he get off under \"Stand Your Ground,\" do you believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, if the evidence shows that he was acting in self-defense and that his fear was reasonable, then yes, under the law that would be an absolute defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Or is this very likely now to go to a trial where a jury will decide?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Well, we don't know yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Can I add to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "If those signs of evidence were actually caused as a result of George Zimmerman starting the altercation -- I mean if for argument's sake he approached Trayvon Martin and began pushing him around, where does that leave him defense under \"Stand Your Ground\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, it's much more difficult if he is the aggressor.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "We don't know much about Trayvon Martin in terms of his condition, do we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "You have -- you put your finger right on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey Anthony"]}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "What was your take on it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, you know, he doesn't have, you know, photographs or videos of a child to sell like Casey Anthony did to raise money for her defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "We go to Alan first for your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I would say he's making a big mistake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Yes or no to an arrest within seven days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Let me be even shorter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Neighborhood watch, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "You know, if you take the right to bear arms, it doesn't mean the right to have a tank in your back garden, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What can it physically, realistically do to change this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Have a bigger lottery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "He's less threatening than a Santorum, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Very quickly, what is the single thing that's made you the most furious since I last saw you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "The single thing is that -- the thing I saw today that we're not training --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "How can that be happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I don't know how.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I think whoever wins in November should put you in there just to foam at them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "How can you not doing more in work training at this time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Then they are putting their two groups -- I can't remember the name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What's he done to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Well, he's done nothing to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "What is the Jewish version of the Tebow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "The Jewish is either -- bringing something up or, you know, a belch, one or the other.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tebow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "The engine's beginning to run again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Did I really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Literally, I've never seen that happen before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CD", "JJ", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "So has Mark Zuckerberg done this because he sees this as a brilliant new tool to enhance Facebook or to crush a potential opponent by buying them out of the market?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I think number two much more than number one.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Zuckerberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2000"]}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Could it be a boom that leads to a quick bubble burst?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "We saw that in 2000.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 550, "question": "It is a slightly mad world, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Well, but I take it -- I take it one of the things -- their claim to fame is that -- yes, is that photographers who think they're good can massage and --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What's the next big sale going to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "I think Path has a shot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "DT", "CD", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "What was it presumed to be worth yesterday and what will it be worth tomorrow, based on Instagram?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "The word on the street is they're raising Around a 250 million valuation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "What will his legacy be, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Well, I think if you look at investigative reporting on television, he was the pioneer in that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Simon Johnson, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I'm fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Simon Johnson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1812"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Central Bank"]}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "CD", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "I love this book title, \"White House Burning,\" because further investigation revealed it's reference to a War of 1812, when war hawks they taxes, didn't fund the military, got rid of the Central Bank.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Founding Fathers"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "What would the Founding Fathers have made of America being 15.6 trillion dollars in debt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Well, the Founding Fathers, first of all, would have been stunned to see the U.S. as the number one world economic and political power.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["15.6 trillion dollars"], "LOCATION": ["America"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Founding Fathers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Come on, just cut to the quick, Romney or Obama, who has -- you have to keep this quite brief -- the best solution, do you think, if it's those two head to head in November, to the economic woes America is facing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "I have problems with both.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"], "PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}]